var quiz = [{"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Preservationism and conservationism are the same thing."}, {"answers": ["Aldo Leopold was among the first ecologists.", "It is the study of the interactions between organisms and their environment.", "This science is anthropocentric.", "Can range from looking at specific environmental issues to interactions between humans and the environment."], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "Which of the following is NOT true about ecology?"}, {"answers": ["Moral extentionists", "Social ecology", "Scientists", "Pragmatists"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Which field of thought would say that until humans are treated equally, environmental ethics are irrelevant?"}, {"answers": ["an ecocentric approach to environmental management", "the naturalistic fallacy", "overpopulation", "inequality among humans"], "correctIndex": 3, "question": "Social ecology argues that environmental problems are caused by _______."}, {"answers": ["Peter Singer", "Gifford Pinchot", "John Muir", "Aldo Leopold"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "_______ is likely to support hunting as long as the animals are harvested sustainably."}, {"answers": ["ecocentric", "stewardship", "utilitarian", "holistic"], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "The _______ view of nature argues that any part of nature that is unused has no value and is therefore wasted."}, {"answers": ["shallow ecology", "scientism", "stewardship", "naturalistic fallacy"], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "The responsibility to care for and protect the environment is known as:"}, {"answers": ["social ecology", "animal rights movement", "pragmatism", "deep ecology"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "The argument that every sentient being deserves to have their suffering minimized or eliminated can be attributed to _______."}, [["Use of the environment is not right or wrong--it depends on how it is used.", "Land Ethic"], ["This thinking is an example of moral extensionism.", "Land Ethic"], ["Natural landscapes have intrinsic value independent\u00a0of their value to humans", "Preservation"], ["Aldo Leopold was a huge supporter for this line of thinking.", "Land Ethic"], ["Natural resources should be used, but sustainably and efficiently.", "Conservation"], ["John Muir was an advocate for this line of thinking.", "Preservation"], ["Humans should keep large portions of the Earth in a natural state. ", "Preservation"], ["Gifford Pinchot was an advocate of this line of thinking.", "Conservation"], ["Land Ethic", "Preservation", "Conservation"]], {"answers": ["Holism", "The dominion thesis", "Moral extensionism", "Deep ecology"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "_______ is the philosophical view that humans are separate from and superior to nature."}, {"answers": ["holism", "pragmatism", "moral extensionism", "scientism"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Disagreements among environmental ethicists may be reconciled through appeals to _______."}, {"answers": ["Calls for an end to any use of animal products or testing, or at least to minimize suffering.", "Considers individual animals, in contrast to the land ethic.", "Argues for the extension of ethical consideration to individual animals.", "The focus of this movement is entirely on domesticated animals, not wild animals."], "correctIndex": 3, "question": "Which of the following is NOT true about the animal liberation movement?"}, {"answers": ["shallow ecology", "ecocentric ecology", "deep ecology", "holistic ecology"], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "The school of thought that emphasizes that society as a whole needs to examine\u00a0its fundamental relationship to the Earth is called what?"}, {"answers": ["utilitarian", "anthropocentric", "holistic", "ecocentric"], "correctIndex": 3, "question": "Deep ecology has a(n) _______ point of view."}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Utilitarians believe that nature has an intrinsic value apart from human use."}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "John Muir argued for the preservation of the Hetch Hetchy Valley wilderness."}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Western ethics tends to be anthropocentric."}, {"answers": ["The valley was flooded and became a reservoir that exists to this day.", "The reservoir was banned and the valley was restored to pristine wilderness.", "It was determined that leaving the area wild would serve the most people.", "The water reservoir was found to have intrinsic value as a natural landscape."], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Which of the following is TRUE regarding the ultimate outcome for the Hetch Hetchy debate?"}, {"answers": ["Pragmatism", "Social ecology", "Scientism", "Holism"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Which of the following is NOT a critique of environmental ethics?"}, {"answers": ["It is an example of moral extensionism", "Suggests that humans should not exploit nature and that it should be left alone.", "It blends ethics and ecology.", "Suggests that use of the environment should prioritize ecological concerns over human ones."], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Which of the following is NOT true about the land ethic?"}, {"answers": ["self-realization", "stewardship", "scientism", "ethics"], "correctIndex": 3, "question": "The philosophy of right and wrong is known as:"}, {"answers": ["Humans should use the environment to their benefit.", "Humans should control nature.", "Humans should leave nature alone as much as possible.", "Humans have a responsibility to care for and protect the environment."], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "Which of the following views does NOT describe beliefs about nature in Western Philosophy?"}, {"answers": ["pragmatism", "social ecology", "holism", "naturalistic fallacy"], "correctIndex": 3, "question": "The statement that, \u201cJust because an ecosystem functions in a certain way doesn\u2019t mean it should\u201d is an example of which critique of environmental ethics?"}]

quizCollection['5'] = quiz
